Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 7 Locals, 2.
  - Local 729 (Norwood)
    - Local 729 (Norwood) Charter, December 1, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 94)
    - Local 729 (Norwood) Leaflet, "Vote For Separate Local", April 29, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 95)
    - Local 729 (Norwood) Separate Charter, May 6, 1946-January 6, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 96)
      - Petition, May 6, 1946; 1-2.
      - Julius Emspak to Lem Markland with Petition, May 17, 1946; 3.
      - Markland to Emspak, June 4, 1946; 4.
      - Petition, June 12, 1946; 5.
      - Emspak to Markland, July 1, 1946; 6.
      - Markland to Emspak, July 10, 1946; 7.
      - Markland to Emspak, July 1, 1946; 8.
      - Hutson Thomas to Emspak, October 17, 1946; 9.
      - Talmadge Raley to Emspak, October 17, 1946; 10.
      - Emspak to Raley, October 23, 1946; 11.
      - Emspak to Markland, October 23, 1946; 12.
      - Arthur Garfield to Ray Klausner, November 20, 1946; 13.
      - Emspak to Markland, November 26, 1946; 14.
      - Markland to Emspak, November 26, 1946; 15.
      - Emspak to Markland, December 2, 1946; 16.
      - Emspak to Waldo Stranger, December 2, 1946; 17.
      - Stranger to Klausner, January 6, 1947; 18.
  - Local 729 (Newcomerstown)
    - Local 729 (Newcomerstown) Officers List, June 15, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 97)
    - Local 729 (Newcomerstown) Incoming Correspondence, June 23-November 4, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - Julius Emspak to Earl Randles Regarding Supplies, June 23, 1937; 1-2.
      - Emspak to B. Pracht Regarding Finances, November 4, 1937; 3.
    - Local 729 (Newcomerstown) Outgoing Correspondence, July 19, 1937-January 22, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 99)
      - B. Pracht to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, November 1, 1937; 1.
      - Pracht to Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 22, 1938; 2.
      - Pracht Letter Regarding Finances, 3.
      - E. Randles to Emspak Regarding Supplies, July 19, 1937; 4.
    - Local 729 (Newcomerstown) Financial Secretary Reports, August 19, 1937-March 7, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 100)
    - Local 729 (Newcomerstown) Supplies, August 23, 1937-March 21, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 101)
    - Local 729 (Newcomerstown) Notice and Requisition, December 1937 (Box 7, Folder 102)
      - Notice of Deliquency, December 1937; 1.
      - Supply Requisition, 2.
  - Local 730
    - Local 730 Officers List, March 21, 1943-January 25, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 103)
    - Local 730 Constitution, May 24, 1943-October 26, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 104)
    - Local 730 Warren Federal Machine and Welder, June 9-October 6, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 105)
    - Local 730 Warren Federal Machine and Welder, June 1, 1937-August 4, 1938 (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Local 730 Membership Resolution of Thanks, August 5, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 107)
    - Local 730 Incoming Correspondence, August 17, 1939-July 25, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 108)
      - Bill Cahn to Robert LeMaster Regarding Materials, February 24, 1947; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Rodney Ziegler Regarding Supplies, August 17, 1939; 2.
      - Emspak to P. Dillon Regarding Wage and Hour Act, December 6, 1940; 3.
      - Emspak to LeMaster, November 25, 1942; 4.
      - Emspak to N. Brant Regarding Finances, April 24, 1944; 5.
      - Emspak to Brant Regarding Finances, December 29, 1944; 6.
      - Emspak to Martin Schwartz Regarding Fees, January 24, 1945; 7.
      - Emspak to Victor Decavitch Regarding Forwarded Letter, February 26, 1945; 8.
      - Emspak to N. Beil Regarding Forwarded Information, February 26, 1945; 9.
      - Emspak to LeMaster Regarding Amalgamation, May 2, 1947; 10.
      - Emspak to LeMaster Regarding Supplies, April 8, 1948; 11.
      - Emspak to LeMaster Regarding Address, March 1, 1948; 12.
      - Emspak to Thelma Price Regarding Financial Report, February 10, 1949; 13.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to LeMaster Regarding Recieved Information, December 11, 1942; 14.
      - Fitzgerald to Beil Regarding Voting, July 16, 1945; 15.
      - Fitzgerald to LeMaster Regarding Granted Aid, February 14, 1947; 16.
      - Fitzgerald to Theodore Thompson Regarding Consititution, July 25, 1949; 17.
      - Fitzgerald to Thompson Regarding Constitution, August 11, 1948; 18.
      - James Matles to Dillon Regarding Organizational Work, March 26, 1941; 19.
      - Matles to William Joseph Regarding Organization Work, October 29, 1941; 20.
      - Matles to LeMaster Regarding Forwarded Letter, October 31, 1941; 21.
      - Matles to Dillon Regarding Salaries, December 11, 1941; 22.
      - David Scribner to Tom Finnerty Regarding Negotiations, July 22, 1946; 23.
      - Scribner to Finnerty Regarding Materials, July 30, 1946; 24.
    - Local 730 Outgoing Correspondence, December 2, 1940-June 17, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 109)
      - N. Beil to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, April 22, 1944; 1.
      - Beil to Emspak Regarding Fees, January 22, 1945; 2.
      - Beil to Emspak Regarding Union Finances, January 27, 1945; 3-4.
      - Beil to Emspak Regarding Membership Obligations, February 20, 1945; 5.
      - Beil to Emspak Regarding Layoff, July 14, 1945; 6.
      - Mary Burn to UE Regarding Materials, April 3, 1946; 7.
      - Burn to Herbert Hirshberg Regarding Amalgamation, May 7, 1946; 8.
      - M. Collins to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, March 30, 1946; 9.
      - Collins to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 11, 1946; 10.
      - Fred D'Avila to Robert LeMaster Regarding Materials, June 17, 1949; 11.
      - P. Dillon to Emspak Regarding Wage and Hour Act, December 2, 1940; 12.
      - Dillon to Emspak Regarding Contact, February 7, 1941; 13.
      - Dillon to James Carey Regarding Contract, March 16, 1949; 14.
      - Dillon to James Matles Regarding Organizational Work, October 27, 1941; 15.
      - Dillon to Matles Regarding Contract, March 24, 1941; 16.
      - Dillon to Emspak Regarding Fingerprinting, March 18, 1942; 17.
      - Dillon to Emspak Regarding Officers, July 24, 1942; 18.
      - Tom Finnerty to Dave Scribner Regarding Negotiations, July 19, 1946; 19.
      - Dillon to Emspak Regarding Officers, July 24, 1942; 20.
    - Local 730 Outgoing Correspondence, December 8, 1942-July 17, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 110)
      - Robert LeMaster to Russel Nixon Regarding Finances, December 8, 1942; 1.
      - LeMaster to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Government Contracts, December 9, 1942; 2.
      - LeMaster to Victor Decavitch Regarding Negotiations, February 11, 1947; 3.
      - LeMaster to Fitzgerald Regarding Contract, February 12, 1947; 4.
      - LeMaster to Julius Emspak Regarding Materials, February 20, 1947; 5.
      - LeMaster to Emspak Regarding Requested Information, April 24, 1947; 6.
      - LeMaster to Emspak Regarding Strike, July 30, 1947; 7.
      - LeMaster to Emspak Regarding Address, February 26, 1948; 8.
      - LeMaster to Emspak Regarding Supplies, March 31, 1948; 9.
      - LeMaster to Emspak Regarding Materials, July 17, 1949; 10.
      - LeMaster to Emspak Regarding Petition, 11.
      - Thelma Price to Emspak Regarding Supplies, February 3, 1949; 12.
      - Price to Emspak Regarding Mailing, September 29, 1949; 13.
      - Arthur Renner to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 19, 1948; 14.
      - Renner to T. Jones Regarding Dues, August 11, 1948; 15.
      - Theodore Thompson to Emspak Regarding Resolution, July 21, 1948; 16.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Constitution, August 9, 1948; 17.
      - Thompson to Emspak Regarding Mailing, June 9, 1949; 18.
      - Thompson to Fitzgerald Regarding Meeting Resolution, June 30, 1940; 19.
      - Thompson to Fitzgerald Regarding Forwarded Letter, July 27, 1949; 20.
      - Charles Whitter to Emspak Regarding Wages, October 3, 1944; 21.
    - Local 730 Separate Charters, October 16-22, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 111)
      - Victor Decavitch to Julius Emspak, October 16, 1942; 1.
      - Emspak to Decavitch, October 22, 1942; 2.
    - Local 730 Correspondence, October 1, 1943-February 21, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 112)
      - Julius Emspak to Congress of Industrial Organizations War Chest Regarding Finances, October 1, 1943; 1.
      - Emspak to Victor Decavitch Regarding Dues, February 2, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Herbert Hirshberg Regarding Amagamation of Locals 706 and 730, April 15, 1946; 3.
      - Hirshberg to Russ Nixon, February 21, 1947; 4.
  - Local 731
    - Local 731 Officers List, January 20, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 113)
    - Local 731 Incoming Correspondence, June 27, 1945-September 3, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 114)
      - Julius Emspak to Sophie Kangas Regarding Fees, June 27, 1945; 1.
      - Emspak to Harold Barnes Regarding Fees, February 17, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Barnes Regarding Finances, May 9, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Barns Regarding Recieved Materials, April 15, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Arthur Atkins Regarding Finances, June 30, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Atkins Regarding Finances, July 18, 1950; 6.
      - Emspak to Atkins Regarding Finances, August 28, 1950; 7.
      - Emspak to K. Richard Regarding Audit, January 5, 1951; 8.
      - Emspak to Richard Regarding Women's Wage Rates, September 3, 1953; 9.
    - Local 731 Outgoing Correspondence, June 18, 1945-August 27, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 115)
      - Arthur Atkins to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 17, 1950; 1.
      - Atkins to Emspak Regarding Finances, 2.
      - Harold Barnes to UE Regarding Addresses, January 20, 1947; 3.
      - Barnes to Emspak Regarding Membership Transfer, February 10, 1947; 4.
      - Barnes to Emspak Regarding Publicity, April 12, 1948; 5.
      - Arthur Hess to Executive Board Regarding Minutes, March 10, 1947; 6.
      - Hess to Pricilla Halmagi Regarding Protest, June 13, 1949; 7.
      - Hess to Lem Markland Regarding Endorsed Action, October 5, 1949; 8.
      - Hess to Phillip Murray Regarding Strike Support, October 5, 1949; 9.
      - Hess to James Matles Regarding Representative, July 11, 1950; 10.
      - Sophie Kangas to Emspak Regarding Fees Waiver, June 18, 1945; 11.
      - K. Richard to Emspak Regarding Audit, January 4, 1951; 12.
      - Richard to Albert Fitzgerald et al Regarding Women's Rates, August 27, 1953; 13.
      - L. Stinsabaugh to Joe Dermody Regarding Resignation, March 2, 1946; 14.
      - Frank Supplee to Emspak Regarding Publicity, October 2, 1950; 15.
    - Local 731 Financial Statement, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Local 731 Leaflet, "Women's Rates", November 11, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 117)
    - Local 731 Organization, January 8, 1944-January 8, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 118)
      - General Electric Regarding Conneaut Charter and Application, December 1944; 1.
      - Julius Emspak to Victor Decavitch, January 8, 1945; 2.
      - Emspak to Walter Barnes, January 8, 1944; 3.
    - Local 731 Conneaut General Electric, January 10, 1956-January 29, 1968 (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Local 731 Conneaut General Electric, April 28, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 120)
    - Local 731 Finances, Sterling Neal to Julius Emspak Regarding Strike, October 6, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 121)
    - Local 731 Strikes, Subsidies and Other Monies, September 25, 1972-April 29, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 122)
  - Local 732 (Warren)
    - Local 732 (Warren) Contract, Packard Electric (Box 7, Folder 123)
    - Local 732 (Warren) Officers List, May 27, 1942-February 1, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 124)
    - Local 732 (Warren) Incoming Correspondence, January 13, 1941-December 22, 1948 (Box 7, Folder 125)
      - Janet Barish to Rosemary King Regarding Finances, May 14, 1948; 1.
      - Bill Cahn to Ken Hostler Regarding Films, March 13, 1947; 2.
      - Cahn to King Regarding Publications, December 22, 1948; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Edward Ryan Regarding Recieved Information, January 13, 1941; 4.
      - Emspak to Margaret Toth Regarding Stoppage, May 14, 1941; 5.
      - Emspak to Toth Regarding Meeting, July 10, 1941; 6.
      - Emspak to Janet Morton Regarding Constitution, December 10, 1941; 7.
      - Emspak to H. Barrnett Regarding Publications, July 1, 1942; 8.
      - Emspak to Victor Decavitch Regarding Publications, June 25, 1942; 9.
      - Emspak to Helen Gaydoch Regarding Bonding, October 13, 1942; 10.
      - Emspak to Lucille Flickenger Regarding Bonding, July 19, 1943; 11.
      - Emspak to King Regarding Check-off Procedures, December 23, 1947; 12.
      - Emspak to King Regarding Finances, June 10, 1948; 13.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Toth Regarding Motion, July 2, 1942; 14.
      - Nathan Geller to Toth Regarding Finances, July 8, 1941; 15.
      - James Matles to Toth Regarding Commendation, May 28, 1941; 16.
      - Matles to Toth Regarding Negotiations, July 31, 1941; 17.
      - Matles to Morton Regarding Employee Transfer, October 3, 1941; 18.
      - Matles to J. Sayers Regarding Rates, October 9, 1941; 19.
      - Matles to Harold Roach Regarding Requested Information, June 18, 1943; 20.
      - Matles to King Regarding Materials, June 30, 1947; 21.
    - Local 732 (Warren) Outgoing Corresondence, January 9, 1941-March 1, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 126)
      - H. Barnett to Julius Emspak Regarding Mailing, November 3, 1941; 1.
      - Barnett to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 7, 1942; 2.
      - John Beskid to Emspak Regarding Conference, April 25, 1945; 3.
      - Mildred Braunns to Emspak Regarding Officer Change, June 11, 1943; 4.
      - Lucille Flickenger to James Matles Regarding Mailing, July 6, 1943; 5.
      - Helen Gaydoch to Emspak Regarding Publication, October 12, 1942; 6.
      - Gaydoch to Emspak Regarding Officers, October 12, 1942; 7.
      - Kenneth Hoslter to Nat Spero Regarding Requested Information, March 1, 1947; 8.
      - Janet Morton Letter Regarding Constitution, September 24, 1941; 9.
      - Morton to Emspak Regarding Constitution, December 4, 1941; 10.
      - Morton to Emspak Regarding Materials, April 3, 1942; 11.
      - Charlotte Pettit to Emspak Regarding Officers List, June 15, 1943; 12.
      - H. Roach to James Matles Regarding Ratification, October 1, 1942; 13.
      - Roach to Harry Anderson Regarding Pay Cut, May 3, 1943; 14.
      - Roach to Matles Regarding Merger, June 2, 1943; 15.
      - Roach to Emspak Regarding Apprenticeship Committee, October 6, 1943; 16.
      - Edward Ryan to Emspak Regarding Officers, January 9, 1941; 17.
      - James Sayers to Matles Regarding Wage Rates, October 7, 1941; 18.
    - Local 732 (Warren) Outgoing Correspondence, May 6, 1941-November 24, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 127)
      - Margaret Toth to Albert Firzgerald Regarding Motion, June 30, 1942; 1.
      - Toth to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 6, 1941; 2.
      - Toth to Matt Geller Regarding Finances, June 19, 1941; 3.
      - Toth to Emspak Regarding Dues, June 21, 1941; 4.
      - Toth to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 27, 1941; 5.
      - Toth to Emspak Regarding Meeting, July 8, 1941; 6.
      - Toth to James Matles Regarding Ratification, July 23, 1941; 7.
      - Local 732 President to Harry Anderson Regarding Negotiations, January 28, 1943; 8.
      - Local 732 Members to Fitzgerald Regarding Organizers, November 24, 1943; 9.
    - Local 732 (Warren) Packard Electric, June 15-21, 1937 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Local 732 (Warren) Charter, January 27, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Local 732 (Warren) Strike, May 7, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 130)
      - Management Proposals, May 7, 1941; 1.
      - Clarification, May 7, 1941; 2.
    - Local 732 (Warren) Lewis Grievance, December 17, 1941-January 2, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 131)
      - Arthur Garfield to Tom Neil, December 17, 1941; 1.
      - Garfield to B.N. McGregor, January 2, 1942; 2.
    - Local 732 (Warren) Membership Drive, January 28-February 26, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 132)
      - Local 732 President to Harry Anderson, January 28, 1943; 1.
      - James Matles to Homer Pierce, February 17, 1943; 2.
      - Pierce to Matles, February 18, 1943; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Pierce, February 26, 1943; 4.
    - Local 732 (Warren) Correspondence, June 29, 1942-October 15, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 133)
      - Victor Decavitch to Julius Emspak Regarding Organization, June 29, 1942; 1.
      - James Matles to Harry Anderson Regarding Grievances, June 30, 1942; 2.
      - Emspak to Neil Brant Regarding Apprenticeship with October 6, 1943, H. Roach Letter to Emspak, October 15, 1943; 3.
  - Local 732 (Tiffin)
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Constitution, June 12, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 134)
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Officers Lists, April 5, 1948-August 17, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 135)
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Incoming Correspondence, June 9, 1949-January 21, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 136)
      - Janet Barish to Dorthy Burch Regarding Requested Information, January 11, 1954; 1.
      - Barish to Nathan Fawcett Regarding Finances, January 21, 1955; 2.
      - Julius Emspak to Angeline Gaietto Regarding Fee Waiver, January 27, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Rosemary King Regarding Bonding, June 9, 1949; 4.
      - Emspak to Ora Eyer Regarding Finances, May 5, 1950; 5.
      - Emspak to Doris Wenner Regarding Fee Waiver, March 10, 1950; 6.
      - Emspak to Rosemary King Regarding Finances, August 28, 1950; 7.
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Outgoing Correspondence, February 19, 1947-June 17, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 137)
      - Angeline Garetto to Julius Emspak Regarding Commendation, February 19, 1947; 1.
      - Rosemary King to James Matles Regarding Taft-Hartley Act, June 25, 1947; 2.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 5, 1947; 3.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Supplies, December 18, 1947; 4.
      - King to David Ratner Regarding Finances, February 16, 1948; 5.
      - King to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, May 24, 1948; 6.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Finances, June 4, 1948; 7.
      - King to Barish Regarding Finances, June 28, 1948; 8.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, June 27, 1950; 9.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Finances, September 11, 1950; 10.
      - King to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 6, 1950; 11.
      - Bulter Stephens to Emspak Regarding Finances, November 25, 1952; 12.
      - Stephens to Joseph Falis Regarding Strike Contribution, June 17, 1955; 13.
      - Doris Wenner to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Fee Waiver, March 7, 1950; 14.
      - Wenner to Emspak Regarding Officer Change, March 14, 1952; 15.
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Finances (Box 7, Folder 138)
      - Statement, 1950; 1.
      - Per Capita, 2.
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Newspaper Clippings, March 7-8, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 139)
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Organization, January 26-27, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 140)
      - Richard Niebur to Julius Emspak, January 26, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Niebur, January 27, 1947; 2-3.
      - Emspak to Lem Markland, January 27, 1947; 4.
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Strike, January 31-February 17, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 141)
      - Notification of Pending Disagreement, January 31, 1949; 1.
      - Strike Report, February 17, 1949; 2.
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Initiation Fees, March 10-April 5, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 142)
      - Julius Emspak to Herbert Hirshberg, March 10, 1950; 1.
      - Rosemary King to Emspak, March 18, 1950; 2.
      - Emspak to King, March 20, 1950; 3.
      - Emspak to King, April 5, 1950; 4.
    - Local 732 (Tiffin) Correspondence, May 10, 1948-June 23, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 143)
      - Herbert Hirshberg to David Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, May 10, 1948; 1.
      - James Matles to Rosemary King, February 3, 1954; 2.
      - Matles to Charles Steiner, June 23, 1955; 3.
  - Local 733
    - Local 733 Officers Lists, July 1947-May 1956 (Box 7, Folder 144)
    - Local 733 Constitution, April 6, 1950-January 31, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 145)
    - Local 733 Minutes, November 4, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 146)
    - Local 733 Incoming Correspondence, July 29, 1947-January 12, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 147)
      - Julius Emspak to John Guerine Regarding Reliance Organization, July 29, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Max Lencl Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, April 28, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to Mavis Kent Regarding Per Capita, November 14, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Kent Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, December 14, 1955; 4.
      - Emspak to Lencl Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, January 12, 1956; 5.
      - Emspak to Adeline Perugine Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, February 17, 1956; 6.
      - Emspak to Perugine Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, February 20, 1956; 7.
      - Emspak to Kent Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, March 16, 1956; 8.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Lencl Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, October 5, 1951; 9.
      - Fred Keller to Lencl Regarding Ward Products Membership, December 29, 1948; 10.
      - James Matles to Lencl Regarding Finances, October 20, 1952; 11.
    - Local 733 Outgoing Correspondence, September 15, 1947-February 20, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Julius Balint to UE Regarding Packinghouse Workers, January 19, 1949; 1.
      - Balint to James Matles Regarding UE Inter-union Rivalry, September 6, 1951; 2.
      - Edna Gates to Matles Regardng Unemployment Organization, March 22, 1954; 3.
      - Mavis Kent to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, October 29, 1952; 4.
      - Max Lencl to Matles, August 11, 1949; 5.
      - Lencl to Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, August 7, 1951; 6.
      - Lencl to Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, September 21, 1951; 7.
      - Lencl to Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, October 13, 1951; 8.
      - Lencl to Matles Regarding Finances, November 6, 1951; 9.
      - Lencl to Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, December 3, 1951; 10.
      - Lencl to Emspak Regarding Finances, April 17, 1952; 11.
      - Lencl Letter Regarding Anti-Communism and Political Action, October 31, 1953; 12.
      - Lencl Letter Regarding Westinghouse Strikes, January 10, 1956; 13.
      - Joan Miller to Emspak Regarding Officers, February 20, 1956; 14.
      - Miller to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Staff Members, January 22, 1951; 15.
      - Henry Notter to Emspak Regarding Organization Dues, September 15, 1947; 16.
      - Eva Welton to Emspak Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, September 13, 1951; 17.
      - George White to Emspak Regarding Organization, March 20, 1948; 18.
      - Local 733 Officers to Phillip Murray Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations and United Steelworkers of America, October 13, 1949; 19.
    - Local 733 Newspaper, Local 733 News, March 31, 1952-June 13, 1955 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Local 733 Leaflets, 1949-1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      - Election Notice Regarding Officers with Ballot, 1949; 1.
      - "We Need More Money" Regarding Negotiations, June 23, 1955; 2.
    - Local 733 Reliance Organization, July 25-November 11, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      - Fred Keller to Julius Emspak, July 25, 1947; 1.
      - Emspak to Lem Markland, July 29, 1947; 2.
      - Emspak to Levern Slagle, July 29, 1947; 3.
      - Emspak to Herbert Hirshberg, October 1, 1947; 4.
      - Memo Regarding Negotiation Session, November 2, 1947; 5.
      - Hirshberg to Emspak, October 6, 1947; 6.
      - Emspak to Hirshberg, October 23, 1947; 7.
      - Markland to Emspak, November 11, 1947; 8.
    - Local 733 Reorganization and Mercury, February 7-March 15, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - Fred Keller to Julius Emspak, February 7, 1948; 1.
      - Emspak to Lem Markland, February 17, 1948; 2.
      - Keller to Emspak, February 26, 1948; 3.
      - Markland to Emspak, February 26, 1948; 4.
      - Emspak to Keller, March 1, 1948; 5.
      - Vern Slagle to Emspak, March 15, 1948; 6.
    - Local 733 IUE Inter-union Rivalry, July-September, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - UE Brief, July 1951; 1.
      - Joseph Persily to James Matles, July 1951; 2.
      - Matles to Persily, July 27, 1951; 3.
      - Persily to Matles, July 27, 1951; 4.
      - David Ratner to Persily, July 29, 1951; 5.
      - Court Order, July 30, 1951; 6.
      - Persily to Ratner, August 1, 1951; 7.